dhakajobs24.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy Policy | Dhaka Jobs 24

**Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:**

Updated: 31-Aug-2014

## Analytics

  * Google Analytics  
Personal Data: Cookie and Usage Data  
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of www.example.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find Google’s [privacy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)[ policy here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).
  * You can opt out by clicking [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)
  * [Shareaholic.com](https://shareaholic.com/ "shareaholic.com") Sharebar and their analytics, their [Shareaholic Privacy Policy](https://shareaholic.com/privacy/) and [Opt Out](https://shareaholic.com/privacy/choices) method.

## Adsense

  * Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google. [Dhaka-jobs.com](http://dhakajobs24.com/ "dhaka-jobs.com") uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks the use of [Dhaka-jobs.com](http://dhakajobs24.com/ "dhaka-jobs.com") and user behavior concerning ads, products and the services we offer.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. You can find the AdSense [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/) here.
  * You may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/blocked-cookies.html).

## What do we do with your data?

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Application to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics and Interaction with external social networks and platforms. By any mean, we don’t use your data for any other purposes.

_**We don’t sell your data, or modify it or use it by any other means.**_

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and .

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [Dhaka-jobs.com](http://dhakajobs24.com/ "dhaka-jobs.com")

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

539/1 West Nakhal Para

Tejgaon Dhaka -1215

Bangladesh
